Um, is that you... Kushida-senpai?
Yes?
It's me!
I was a year behind you in
middle school—Yagami Takuya.
Yagami...
Oh, Yagami-kun?!
Yes! It's been a while, hasn't it?
You know this guy?
Yes, we didn't interact very much,
but he made a big impression
because he was so smart!
Do you know this Yagami person, too?
I feel so lucky to get to go to
the same school as you again!
You went to the same middle school, right?
I'm afraid not.
I didn't have time to notice
people who didn't concern me.
Do you think Yagami knows
about Kushida's past?
I wouldn't be surprised.
I know it's sudden, but I
feel like I can trust you.
Would you be my partner
for the special test?
You're all right with me?
Wouldn't you rather be with
someone a bit smarter?
I'm still finding my way at this school,
so what I really want is
a partner I can trust!
Um... can you give me some
time to think about it?
Oh, of course!
I won't partner up with anyone
until you give me your answer.
Classroom of the Elite 4th Season 2nd Year 1st Term
I admired you so much!
#2 Contract and Payment
Isn't that cool?
Look at this!
Awesome!
Man, those first-years don't
have a care in the world.
And here we are running ourselves ragged
looking for good partners...
Have you forgotten how
you acted a year ago?
O-Of course not!
I just know better now.
So we're looking for a first-year
willing to partner with Sudo?
I thought we should ask around, at least.
Could we speak with you?
We're searching for partners
for the upcoming special test.
Could we speak with you?
Oh, of course.
Right?
Yes, we haven't found
partners yet ourselves.
Thank you for being so forthcoming.
We're looking for someone to
partner with Sudo-kun here.
How about this, then?
What, we gotta pay you with points?
And 50,000? What a rip-off!
Oh, Senpai, don't be ridiculous.
It's not 50,000. It's 500,000.
F-Five hundred thousand?!
We've already had offers
from Class A and Class C.
We're going to get the best offer we can.
Very well. We'll consider it.
That said, we have another request.
Could you introduce us to
other Class D students?
Well... that might be difficult.
Yeah. Hosen-kun'll get mad
if we fall out of line.
Right?
Bastards. Takin' advantage
of us like that...
And Hosen-kun gets mad if they
fall out of line, they said.
But aren't they gonna end up
without partners by the deadline?
It's the second-years who have the most
to fear from failing to find partners.
Hosen-kun wants to use that to extort
large numbers of points from us.
Continuing to ask around will
likely yield the same results.
How will you approach it?
I won't attempt to engage
with the money game.
The most we can earn from this test
is fifty class points for first place.
Converting that to private points,
it's just a little over two million.
In other words,
paying 500,000 per student means
you're in the red after five.
Which means throwing points at
the problem isn't a solution.
I think our best chance is
to negotiate with Class 1-D.
That said, relying solely on
Hosen-kun's class seems risky.
To find an excellent partner,
we'll have to continue asking
as many people as possible.
Hello!
There's an excellent partner
right here, actually!
You were eavesdropping on us?
What a thing to say, Senpai!
I just happened to overhear,
so I spoke up.
I'm Amasawa Ichika of Class 1-A.
I have an A ranking in
Academic Achievement.
Would you like to work with me?
I appreciate the offer,
but would you be willing to work
with Sudo-kun here instead?
Your academic rating is E+, I see...
Well, I'm willing to lend you a hand.
You mean it?!
I just love strong men, see?
What are you talking about?
I don't mean strength of will or anything.
I mean physically strong!
Maybe I'll find a lot of strong
men and have them slug it out.
Whoever comes out on
top will be my partner!
Is this some kind of joke?
You obviously can't do that.
Joke? No, I'm very serious.
I just love strong men.
Let's go, Suzune.
She's just making fun of us.
I believe you're right.
Okay, fine!
I'll give you another chance
if you'll forgive me.
A chance?
After strong men, I love men who can cook!
If you can make a delicious dish that
I request, I'll partner up with you.
C-Cook?! I've never cooked before...
You wouldn't allow me
to cook for you instead?
Nope!
I told you, I love men who can cook.
Ayanokoji-kun.
I believe you've bragged to me
about your cooking skills before.
Yes.
It's no exaggeration to say that
cooking is my strongest field.
Would you accept Ayanokoji-kun, then?
Fine, but are you really good at cooking?
My standards are extremely high!
He can handle it. Right?
Yes, I suppose.
Well, then, it's a deal!
If you fail to cook me a delicious
home-cooked meal tomorrow after class,
the whole deal's off.
I'm counting on you, Ayanokoji!
Please cook me up a partner!
Tomorrow it is, then! Bye-bye!
Horikita, I believe you're aware
that my cooking skill is—
Be quiet now. I'll think up a plan.
Advanced Nurturing High School Staff
Update: 34 new partnerships have formed.
The current number of partners is 56.
Fifty-six pairs have formed
as of this morning.
Over a third of the student
body has partnered up by now.
I'd better start getting serious, too.
Good morning, Ayanokoji-senpai.
I apologize for Hosen-kun's
actions the other day.
You don't need to apologize for that.
Well... I tagged along to make
sure he didn't do anything rash,
and I deeply regret that I failed.
Well-mannered and polite,
with excellent grades.
Why is she in Class D?
And of greater concern to me is...
the way she looked at me then.
Do you have a partner yet?
Me?
No, not yet. A few people
have made offers, but...
Couldn't both Class Ds work together
to find partners with each other?
You mean like... an alliance?
Yes.
I'm in favor of that.
There's one problem, though.
Hosen, you mean?
Yes. Most of our students are
keeping their heads down and
doing what Hosen-kun tells them.
Are you in a special
position within your class?
You don't seem particularly cowed by him.
I refuse to be intimidated by violence!
But if it's Hosen who
decides your class policy,
I doubt he'll agree to the offer I made.
Um... if you're all right with it,
despite the situation,
I could set us up a negotiation?
You're sure about that?
I'm sure Horikita would appreciate that.
Is Horikita-senpai your class's leader?
Yes. I'll let her know.
Could we trade contact information?
Yes. I look forward to working
with you, Ayanokoji-senpai!
That was a surprisingly assertive
move, coming from you.
Should I not have done it?
No, it's wonderful.
But it seems Hosen wants to play the
money game you're trying to avoid.
You're right.
But are points really all he's after?
You think he's targeting us somehow?
Still, I can't imagine
he'll be easy to deal with.
As insurance, I'm discussing a potential
alliance with part of Class 1-B.
Would that involve Yagami,
that boy who went to middle school
with you and Kushida?
Kushida-san partnered
up with him yesterday.
I'm having her negotiate
through him behind the scenes.
I'd like you to do your part, as well.
Amasawa, you mean?
Yes.
I've figured out a plan.
First, you need a cutting board, right?
And a chef's knife, right?
And you'll need a bowl and a whisk...
Wait a minute.
I have cooking supplies in my room.
It's fine. I want you to
have a set just for me!
These are all expensive brands, too.
Of course, you'll need a Petty knife, too!
May I ask a question?
Who's paying for—
You are, of course! Silly.
I knew that, of course.
Well, I guess it's an investment
in high-quality equipment.
Oh, I told you, these are just for me.
Don't waste them on anyone else, okay?
She's a monster.
Coming in!
Wow, it's so nice and tidy!
You can make yourself at
home while I'm cooking.
Thanks, Senpai!
Oh, and no looking at your
phone while you cook!
How strict.
Can't handle it?
Of course I can.
I'll put my phone right here.
So, what dish do you want?
Here comes the big announcement!
The dish I want you to cook is...
Tom yum goong!
Tom yum goong?
I can't wait, Senpai!
I heard everything.
I wasn't expecting tom yum goong...
Please walk me through it.
I taught you yesterday
how to use your knives.
We're going to aim for fifteen
to thirty minutes of prep time.
Is that all right?
Let's see how far I've come in a day.
Wow, awesome! If we're going
on looks, it's a pass for sure!
Okay, let's eat!
I love the cilantro!
And you made bunny apple slices!
Thank you for the meal.
Senpai, your tom yum goong...
I'd say it's pretty decent!
First, let me clean this up.
I'll handle that.
Hey, it's no big!
I asked such a big favor.
Let me handle this much.
Okay, then.
By the way, about your judgment...
Well, honestly, it shouldn't be a pass,
but you bought me all
this expensive stuff...
So, in honor of your efforts,
I guess I'll pair up with Sudo-senpai.
I'm grateful.
Hey, no prob!
Just don't forget that gratitude, okay?
Anyway, I don't wanna stay too
late, so I'm heading home.
Sure.
Later, Ayanokoji-senpai!
Bye-bye!
Well done.
It seems to have worked.
The Sudo problem is solved.
That's an important accomplishment.
Though I feel we were saved
by Amasawa's generous judging.
I'll let you know when
Nanase contacts me next.
Right.
If Amasawa is the White Room student,
I'd expect her to have
rigged something here...
but what matters is that she's
partnering with Sudo, not me.
Normally, that would
clear her of suspicion of being
the White Room student, but...
Nanase Tsubasa
I can meet you after class tomorrow
It seems the students we talked
to got another offer from Class C.
They said they'd give them 10,000
points to refuse Class A's offer.
What are they, stupid?
It seems Ryuen-kun is determined
to take the fight to me.
What are you going to do?
Tell the first-years that I'm
prepared to match Ryuen-kun's offer.
But even if the first-years agree to it,
don't actually form the partner contract.
What in the world?
I don't understand at all.
Ryuen-kun... your strategy
is working to my benefit.
I'm not following this all.
Sounds fine to me. If the
princess says she doesn't need it...
Ryuen-kun's naked attempt at bribery...
It's not bad in and of itself.
But it was a mistake to compete with
us over the exact same students.
But to be able to offer
up bribes like that,
they must have a lot of private
points saved up, right?
I'm not convinced.
It doesn't cost anything
just to offer a bribe.
So they're just pretending
to have the money?
How does that benefit Class C, exactly?
Without Ryuen-kun there,
we of Class A would attract
the most excellent students
through our brand power alone.
But with Class C offering bribes,
we're forced to play the money game, too.
What's his next move, then?
Drive up the price, and try to force us
to expend as many points as possible.
I get it. Like a poker game.
But he's misjudged me...
and the brand power of Class A.
Apparently, the Class B first-years
we'd enticed for 200,000
are entertaining more offers.
But why? Is 200,000 not enough for them?
Calm down.
I know just what they're after.
Tell them we'll pay 100,000 up front,
and 200,000 after the test.
Y-You serious?
That won't be enough to
lock down most of them.
They'll expect Sakayanagi to go higher.
You sure this won't just
blow up in our faces?
Even if we both offer the same amount,
their brand power will carry the day.
The brand power of
Class A is a temporary thing.
Still, what if the bidding keeps going up?
We don't actually have to pay.
What I'm trying to do
is take the measure of the people
in the first-year classes.
Anyone who would flip over money
is someone we can get
on our side at any time.
What matters is everyone else.
I was never going to pay out
pocket-change levels of
class points on this test.
To kill Class A, I need to wait
for when far more class points
are being thrown around.
Oh, I don't see you here often.
Hello, Shiina-san.
We'd like to talk, so it
may get a little loud today.
I see.
In that case, there are seats back
there that would be suitable.
Thank you.
Are things going well in Class C?
Yes, it seems they're really moving along.
Nanase-san aside, we need to
know what Hosen-kun might do.
Yes.
Whether he shows up today will
greatly change our approach.
Sorry I'm late, Senpai.
Horikita Suzune.
Thank you for making time
to meet with us today.
I'm... I should say...
My name is Nanase Tsubasa.
Really, I should be thanking you.
To get right to the point,
my proposal is not
to pay points in exchange for a contract.
I understand.
You want a proper alliance,
with both sides covering for the other's
students with poor Academic Achievement.
Yes. If you were aware of
that when you came here,
can I assume there's room for negotiation?
Well... I hope so.
Hosen-kun's strategy is rooted
in personal self-interest.
At this rate, the students with low
Academic Achievement won't be able to
find partners by the day of the test.
But what I'm most afraid of
is that his self-interest will
take precedence moving forward,
and our class unity will fall apart.
True. Too much focus on self-interest
will leave you at a major disadvantage
in future tests that require class unity.
Yes.
That's why I chose to undertake
these negotiations myself,
for the sake of our class.
Then let me ask a rather bold question.
How many students in Class 1-D are
currently struggling to find a partner?
About fifteen at the moment.
That's more than I expected.
Nanase-san, if possible,
I'd like to arrange a rather
large contract with you.
A large contract?
You and I will determine and finalize
fifteen partnerships between ourselves.
That's an excellent proposal,
but Hosen-kun will never agree
to help you without payment.
But why? It won't disadvantage
him in any way.
But even so...
I don't think he'll allow it.
I see. So that's the situation.
I've learned one thing
about how Hosen thinks.